<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>VidyaSikha Blog</title>
        <link>https://vidyasikha.github.io/Notes/blog</link>
        <description>VidyaSikha Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blog notes]]></title>
            <link>https://vidyasikha.github.io/Notes/blog/create-blog</link>
            <guid>https://vidyasikha.github.io/Notes/blog/create-blog</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Markdown front matter for Blog post]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Markdown front matter for Blog post</p><h2 class="anchor anchorWithHideOnScrollNavbar_WYt5" id="markdown-front-matter-for-blog-post">Markdown front matter for Blog post<a href="#markdown-front-matter-for-blog-post" class="hash-link" aria-label="Direct link to Markdown front matter for Blog post" title="Direct link to Markdown front matter for Blog post">​</a></h2><ul><li><strong>Tags</strong>: A list of labels or objects representing tags that can be associated with your blog post. Each tag can have a label and a permalink.</li><li><strong>Table of Contents Minimum Heading Level</strong>: Specifies the minimum heading level (ranging from 2 to 6) to be shown in the table of contents. It should be equal to or lower than the maximum heading level.</li><li><strong>Table of Contents Maximum Heading Level</strong>: Specifies the maximum heading level (ranging from 2 to 6) to be shown in the table of contents.</li><li><strong>Keywords</strong>: An array of keywords associated with the blog post. These keywords are used as meta tags for search engines, improving discoverability.</li><li><strong>Description</strong>: The first line of the Markdown content serves as the description of the document. It is used as a meta tag for search engines and also in social media sharing.</li><li><strong>Image</strong>: An optional cover or thumbnail image that can be associated with the blog post. This image is displayed when sharing the link to the post.</li><li><strong>Slug</strong>: Allows customization of the URL for the blog post. It determines the path for the blog post URL, which typically follows the pattern "/routeBasePath/slug". The slug can be a simple string, a file path, or even a full URL path.</li><li><strong>sidebar_label</strong></li><li><strong>sidebar_position</strong></li></ul>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>docusaurus blog</category>
            <category>docusaurus</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>